Track 10.2 Unit 10 Grammar Activity 1
Bài 10.2 Đơn vị 10 Ngữ pháp Bài tập 1
Listen and circle T true or F false
Nghe và khoanh tròn T đúng hoặc F sai
Are you going to go on holiday in the summer?
Bạn có đi nghỉ mát vào mùa hè không?
Yes, we are. We're going to visit Jordan. Are you going to travel by train?
Có. Bọn mình sẽ đến thăm Jordan. Bạn sẽ đi bằng tàu hỏa à?
No, we aren't. We're going to travel by plane
Không. Bọn mình sẽ đi bằng máy bay
Who are you going to visit?
Bạn sẽ đến thăm ai?
My uncle and his family
Chú và gia đình chú
What are you going to do there? I'm going to play with my cousins
Bạn sẽ làm gì ở đó? Mình sẽ chơi với các anh chị em họ
Are you going to speak Arabic?
Bạn sẽ nói tiếng Ả Rập không?
Yes, I am. I'm going to speak Arabic and English
Có. Mình sẽ nói tiếng Ả Rập và tiếng Anh